Rodrigo Antonio Guzmán Castro

Phone: +56-9-50503351- email: rodrigoguzman1202@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodrigo-guzman-a5277115b/

Portfolio: https://lkaza.github.io/

Professional Profile

Technical Artist with 2 years of experience in Unity3D, mostly in charge of importing character and 3D models into Unity and creating different effects using Shaderlab with URP that improve the performance of the visuals.

Over my carreer I've been working with Artists to ensure the art looks the way the want to, I've learned Blender software to understand the creative process in 3D Stylized characters

Technical Skills

- Programming Languages:
 - o 2 years of C#.
 - o 1 year of ShaderLab.
 - o 2 years Relational databases SQL.
 - o Java.
 - o Javascript.
 - o MongoDB.
 - o Javascript.
 - o NodeJS.
- Agile methodology Scrum and Kanban.
- Particle System in Unity.
- VFX Graph.
- Amplify Shader Editor/Shader Graph.
- Repositories Git/Github.
- Generalist 3D Blender.
 - o Poly Modelling, UV Map, Textures, Rigging.

Employment

Imaginima – Personal Studio (Fondos de cultura – Chile Founding) April 2022 -Present

Technical Artist and VFX Artist.

- Ensure performance using Baked Illumination and Occlusion Culling.
- UI Develop and backend for Inventory System capable of being used with navigation new input system.
- Established work pipeline for 3D characters.
- In charge of shaders, textures and some 3D with rigging and animations.

YPF

Leading company in exploration, exploitation, distillation, distribution and production of electricity, gas, oil and derivatives. With presence throughout Chile and Argentina.

Network Admin (TI)

June 2019 - December 2019

- In charge of connections of users in integrated Enterprise system.
- Set up new devices and help new employees of YPF with their new devices (Phones-Tablets-Laptops).
- Weekly reports to managers to ensure meeting deadlines.

Personal Projects

NovaKajo (Self Developments).

Tecnical prototype of multiplayer server-client Arquitecture of Headworld.

Headworld - 2021

Graphics Programmer

January 2021-February-2021

- Recieve network package and reflect animations for characters.
- Day and Night System.
- Deactivate objects far from player.
- Shader development be it water foutnain, lava,.. etc.
- 3D character import and animation blending between them

KeloWar – 2021

- Tecnical prototype of Android development.
- Very similar to game "Archero".

Rem - 2021

- 3D model from scratch to rig/textura in blender.
- Physics management with Magica Cloth asset from unity store.
- Toon shader using Unity Chan and others toon shaders to achieve anime-looking style.

PyroBoom (GMTK Game Jam) – 2020

- Procedural map for endlesss survival.
- Animated through code using C#.

Education

2013 - 2019	Engineering Informatics Bachelor's Degree – Universidad de Playa Ancha – Valparaíso
	-Mención en Gestión de la Información

Seminaries and Courses

Junio 2020	Math For Video Games: The Fastest Way To Get Smarter At Math - Udemy
Mayo 2020	RPG Core Combat Creator: Learn Intermediate Unity C# Coding - Udemy
Marzo 2020	Complete C# Unity Game Developer 3D - Udemy